In conclusion, there are four key points you
need to remember in today's lesson.
The first one is that you should always
read the requirement carefully to not exceed the word limit.
Second is making predictions is an essential step.
Before you listen, you have to predict some
paraphrases to help you listen in an attentive
and active way.
When making predictions for each blank, you need
to base on their grammatical structures and the
context of conversations.
The third, you should always check the answers
to correct grammatical mistakes such as singular nouns
and plural nouns.
And the last thing is that you have
to practice.
The only way to boost your score is
to practice regularly.
I hope that you will study hard and
get your desired score.
I'll see you in the next lesson.
Goodbye.